<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Fate Campaign lore]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/</link><image><url>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Fate Campaign lore</title><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 20:02:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 20:02:25 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[MD]]></copyright><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator>MD</dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Alaya]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>  Alaya is the collective unconsciousness of mankind and the drive for its survival as a whole. Alaya constantly steers mankind away from extinction. Alaya used to be part of <a data-href="Gaia" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/gaia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Gaia</a>, but it later broke off due to humans becoming advanced enough to to independent from Gaia. Hypothetically, if another species were to become advanced as humans, they would likely have something similar.<br>    Gaia does not like this very much, as it sees humanity going kinda out of control and increasingly perceives humans as a source of threat due to their reckless destruction of the environment. So tldr Gaia hates Alaya.<br>    Human Order, also referred to as the&nbsp;Common Sense of Man**, is the core principle on which Alaya operates for the building of the&nbsp;Human Order Foundation. Essentially, it is the principle that "humanity must exist for as long as possible".&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Counter Force" data-href="The Counter Force" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-counter-force.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Parallel Worlds</a>&nbsp;in which humanity has destroyed itself or advanced too quickly and therefore stopped progressing are, following this principle, culled, allowing for only the most promising Parallel Worlds to survive in order to ensure the future of mankind.&nbsp;Should it be overturned or compromised, the fabric of time would fall apart and humanity would be doomed.<br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.<br>
  Info known by higher positions or specific fields in The Mage's Association.<br>
  Info known by Specific divisions of the church of the Church.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/alaya.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Alaya.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 16:52:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Current Events]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>After The Events of the 5th Fuyuki Holy Grail War, the truth about the Holy Grail being a door to The Root was revealed to those of prominence in the Mage's Association, but was kept fairly secret. That is until The American Holy Grail War happened in 2009, causing this truth to spread far and wide in the World of Magecraft.<br>Many magi found the prospect of reaching The Root this way as an opportunity that they cannot let slip by their hands any further, while the majority of the mages in the World of Magecraft found the idea repulsive, as it is an insult to their lineage and craft, to rely on some flawed ritual made by another would be a magus' disgrace.<br>For now many eagerly await the rise of a new Holy Grail war one that will invite many more eyes than the last and influence the actions of most Factions in the World of Magecraft.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/current-events.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Current Events.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 22:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dead Apostles]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>  Dead Apostles are humans that became vampires either by the use of magecraft (though this kind is rare) or by the actions of another vampire of similar nature (in this case, either a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="True Ancestors" data-href="True Ancestors" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/true-ancestors.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">True Ancestor</a> or another Dead Apostle). The Dead Apostles also includes creatures that weren't humans, such as animals.<br>
Among the creatures that fall under the vampire category, they are the most numerous.<br>
    They are the main targets of the Executors of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Church" data-href="The Church" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-church.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Burial Agency</a>, an organization that exterminates the Dead Apostles and seals The Twenty-seven Dead Apostle Ancestors.<br><br>    The original dead apostles were created to act as countermeasures in the case of a True Ancestor being overwhelmed by their thirst for blood. In exchange for losing their free will and becoming a tool to relieve the vampiric impulses of the True Ancestors as emergency meals, these individuals were granted powers and longevity similar to their masters. However, what they received was still a flawed form of&nbsp;immortality&nbsp;and it was soon discovered that they needed to suck the blood of others to survive.<br>  Dead apostles have&nbsp;Vampiric Impulses&nbsp;which pushes them to suck the blood of others, and they also have the physical need to suck the blood of others in order to maintain their own bodies. For those Dead Apostles who used to be human, it is something not entirely dissimilar from love.<br>    The result of repeatedly sucking the blood of humans was the emergence of a sense of superiority in the heart of the servants of the True Ancestors. Such a thing eventually gave birth to a feeling of rebellion towards their masters, which then lead the servants to find ways of strengthening their mental control and escaping from True Ancestors. After the rebellion, these blood-sucking humans became known as the Dead Apostles.<br>    Dead Apostles first started appearing frequently around 20~100 AD deeming magi as their enemies and attacking them. Every Crusade was marked by the appearance of a Dead Apostle on the battlefield, each attacking humans indiscriminately on all sides of the war.<br>    Although the Dead Apostles are maverick and individualistic by nature, there is a form of ruling body among them: The Twenty-seven Dead Apostle Ancestors.<br><br>The Dead Apostle Ancestors have existed for three thousand years. They are primarily individualistic, with the exclusion of the five members of the Age of Gods Alliance, and not every Dead Apostle Ancestor is an enemy of mankind.<br>
The oldest Dead Apostle Ancestors are referred to as Elder Title: League of the Age of Gods. Each Dead Apostle Ancestor creates and rules over it's own kingdom and they divide the world of Dead Apostles into 27 powers. <br>The original twenty-seven were those who were able to escape their existence as "emergency rations" for the True Ancestors. As of the modern day, there are the "elders" of the BC era and the "upstarts" of the AD era.<br>As of modern day, some positions have been rendered empty, the total verified being twenty-one as of the 2010s AD. <br>Each Dead Apostle Ancestor has a&nbsp;Principle&nbsp;associated with them, also known as "the seeds of textural rules").&nbsp;It is a sort of curse that manifests as a unique power distinct from their other properties as a vampire.<br><br><br>Idea Blood: Hemonomic Principle&nbsp;is the blood that makes an Ancestor an Ancestor. It can either be inherited or created. the inheritance of the Idea Blood will raise the inheritor to a Rank IX Ancestor regardless of their original rank. Magi who became Dead Apostles and then later became Dead Apostle Ancestors are those who created their own Idea Blood through a vast amount of time and research.<br>Normally, the Idea Blood remains after the defeat of an Ancestor and manifests as a pulsing red fruit that looks like coagulated blood and their corresponding Principle would be lost.<br><br>Although they appear to have capacities beyond human limitations, most vampires actually acquired their powers by constantly refining&nbsp;human-inherent abilities&nbsp;throughout their extended lives. In other words, anyone with a similarly long lifespan has the potential to reach a level comparable to the Dead Apostles. The Dead Apostles also lost the human ability to procreate.<br>Contrary to popular belief, Vampirification is not the transformation of the body, but of existence. It’s like if the entry in <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The planes of Existence" data-href="The planes of Existence" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-planes-of-existence.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">the&nbsp;Root</a> &nbsp;that read ‘human’ changed class to ‘Dead Apostle’ — it means that one has become a vampire in one’s very being. So one cannot undo Vampirification by putting your soul into another human physical body. Also vampires can be killed with conventional weaponry. However, that is a feat near impossible to accomplish due to their superior abilities when compared to a normal human.<br>
Vampire blood itself contains Ether, which holds the power to materialize whatever they want, but it is limited to the form their soul takes.<br>Dead Apostles need a near regular uptake of blood as their bodies are constantly degenerating, and once they die, they won't leave a trace as their bodies turn into ash. This allows them to absorb genetic information and stabilize their own bodies.<br>
High ranking Dead Apostles with underlings can have these ones procure the blood in their stead and they still will receive that blood no matter the distance (we got WIFI blood here).<br><br>Dead Apostles who suck the blood of humans and replace it with their own pass on the curse of vampirism, as their victims are now reborn as vampires under the control of their sire. The curse of vampirism is divided into several steps according to its depth and the name of each step is derived from the Church. The Dead Apostles themselves see the depth of the curse as a caste system, of social standing in vampiric society, in which Rank I-III are slaves, Rank IV-V are subordinates and Rank VI-IX are vampires<br>When a human becomes a vampire, their body often will transform into the most beautiful form it can take, a process which can change both the vampire’s apparent physical age and physical features.<br>
<br>
Rank I: Corpse  — A marionette dancing to the tune of its sire. A being that had it's blood sucked and then replaced with that of the sire's. A mere grunt which simply sucks blood and delivers it to it's sire. One of what are called "The Dead".

<br>
Rank II:&nbsp;Ghoul&nbsp; — A corpse mimicking the form it had in life, possessing a will yet incapable of coherent thought. While its sire's magical energy keeps it from decaying, its insides have completely disintegrated. As the brain's decomposition causes it to seek flesh and blood instinctively, it is more savage than a Rank l, as they can devour people in less than a few minutes. A 100% loyal soldier that can be programmed by its sire, it also dies with it's sire's death or by the sire's decision to cut off their magical energy connection.  Counted among "The Dead".

<br><br>
<br>
Rank III:&nbsp;Undead&nbsp; — From this point on a creature that can finally be called a vampire. A living corpse, that hasn't fully regained its mental faculties and lacks its sense of pain and taste, but can simulate a human lifestyle on its own. A high-ranking soldier whose brain has been reconstructed after death, that follows its sire after understanding what kind of creature it has become. They are still bound to their sire and return to being corpses when their sire gets destroyed or by the sire's decision that they are not needed anymore. These undead act as commanders to the lower ranked Dead and are not fazed by sunlight, but require periodic embalming treatment in order to conceal their true nature. Counted among "The Dead".

<br>
Rank IV:&nbsp;Nightkin&nbsp;— An undead who acts as a fledgling vampire while maintaining its original personality. A half-human vampire whose inhuman physical abilities come at the cost of experiencing extreme coldness and thirst. A low-ranking knight, that according to the Church can hold its own against one of their Executors. When those of Rank Ⅵ and above carefully drink the blood of their prey, their victim starts out as a vampire of this rank. They may become anemic under the sunlight, though it doesn't burn them yet.<br>
In the&nbsp;magical world, one is considered "a person" upon reaching to this rank. It can now survive away from its sire. From the sire's point of view it has changed from an "object" to a "living thing", in a sense. Only one in a thousand people are able to reach this rank.

<br>
Rank V:&nbsp;Nightmare — Adding to the scope of Rank Ⅳ, at this point the curse within their blood allows them to manifest special powers deriving from their sire or perhaps arising from their own self. 

<br>
Rank VI:&nbsp;Dead Apostle (Inferior)&nbsp; — A completely self-sufficient bloodsucker, who has lost the human ability to procreate. Though these Lords can create children through their bloodsucking incursions, they cannot sire a child that can exceed Rank Ⅵ — what you'd call a limit to these upstarts. Only one out of ten thousand people are able to reach this rank.

<br>
Rank VII:&nbsp;Dead Apostle (Superior) — Greater Dead Apostle. Those of Rank Ⅵ who were acknowledged by an Ancestor and bestowed with additional abilities. Though they share a name, this rank is of a wholly different scale from the previous one. To reach this rank is to become a poison that taints the land simply by existing.<br>
They are a heresy that ordinary&nbsp;Executors&nbsp;cannot cross blades with, noble vampires permitted their own free will. Greater Dead Apostles do not show absolute obedience to their parent Ancestors; given the chance they can defeat them and inherit their curse. 

<br>
Rank VIII:&nbsp;Successor&nbsp; — A talented vampire chosen by an Ancestor as their own successor. A prince or princess, who is in a position to inherit the Idea Blood of a Dead Apostle Ancestor upon that Ancestor's destruction.<br>
Assuming a minimum of two for each Ancestor, there are more than fifty Rank Ⅷ individuals. Some of them are even said to have been created in imitation of the True Ancestors. 

<br>
Rank IX:&nbsp;Ancestor&nbsp;— The old Dead Apostles who broke free from their role as emergency rations and achieved victory in their struggle for independence as wholly distinct beings. 

<br><br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.<br>
  Info known by higher positions or specific fields in The Mage's Association.<br>
  Info known by Specific divisions of the church of the Church.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/dead-apostles.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Dead Apostles.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 18:03:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250214003433.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250214003433.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gaia]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>  The&nbsp;World&nbsp;is used to refer to either the Earth,&nbsp;Gaia. It is the actual Will of the Planet as it is living being in of itself, it is&nbsp;kinda primal, and composed of everything that lives on it, to a degree.<br>  It acts on its own to ensure its survival and has countermeasures placed to ensure that, one of the most important ones is that the destruction of the planet by Earth-born creatures is essentially impossible due to measures already put in place by <a data-href="The Counter Force" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-counter-force.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Counter Force</a>. Even Anti-Planet&nbsp;Noble Phantasms&nbsp;are unable to accomplish this feat.<br><br>The time period beginning with the genesis of the Earth 4.5 billion years ago until the beginning of the Common Era around 1 AD is referred to as the&nbsp;*Age of Gods**, during which the world followed laws based not on physics but on&nbsp;<a data-href="Mystery" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/mystery.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Mystery</a>.<br>The Age of Gods period is marked by a greater proliferation of&nbsp;Phantasmal Species&nbsp;and greater interaction between Gods and mortals. This is the age of heroes and mythology, when rules of mankind and the laws of the world were different right down to the very fundamental physics of reality itself. Even magecraft was nearly on par with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Magecraft" data-href="Magecraft" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/magecraft.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> in the Age of the Gods.<br>Due to a fuckload of shit the Age of the Gods started deteriorating doomed to end at some point which ended with Mystery being weakened TREMENDOUSLY and the Gods losing their powers and becoming&nbsp;Divine Spirits, forced to exist likely in the&nbsp;Reverse Side of the World, only able to observe the Earth without directly interfering.<br><br> The&nbsp;Ultimate Ones&nbsp;are vessels upon which the planet's will is manifested, and rather than being part of the&nbsp;Counter Force, they are essentially the planets themselves. Unlike most other celestial bodies in the Solar System, there is no clear Ultimate One for Earth. The creature closest to being the Ultimate One of Earth is&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://typemoon.fandom.com/wiki/Archetype:_Earth" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" title="Archetype: Earth" href="https://typemoon.fandom.com/wiki/Archetype:_Earth" target="_blank">Archetype Earth</a><br> For Example, on of the most well spread horror stories in the World of Magecraft is about the Ultimate One ORT, the&nbsp;One Radiant Thing that is currently residing in South America. It was known as a dormant being that killed all who approached it instantly, no&nbsp;magus&nbsp;stepping into its territory having ever returned alive. After a certain incident in the 16th century that ended with the death 6 of the strongest mages at the time, all Attempts to interact with it have ceased.<br>
Brishisan, founder and acting director of the Clock Tower, later stated, "Only the planet's screams will awaken ORT. It's hibernating nice and cozy in South America's underground. So you keep your hands off it. The planet will lose its anthroposphere if that thing starts moving."<br>
Now it is a story used to scare children, the literal Boogeyman of the World of Magecraft.<br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/gaia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Gaia.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 16:36:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magecraft]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>  Magecraft is the artificial reenactment of <a data-href="Mystery" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/mystery.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Mystery</a>, which is normally possible only to inhuman beings.<br>
The limits of magecraft have changed with time, as science evolved and Magic from the past became possible through science.<br>
There exists no impossibility for modern magecraft within the rules of the world and limits of human intellect; there are limitations however, since magecraft acts as the reenactment of preexisting phenomena, it is impossible to use it to create new Mysteries. There exists a "Wall" that stops human wisdom from doing so. Getting past this "wall" is known as Magic.<br>  Magecraft draws upon a predetermined power from the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The planes of Existence" data-href="The planes of Existence" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-planes-of-existence.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Root</a>. However, because that amount of power is fixed, the more people draw from it, the more its capacities become mundane. In short, the greater is the collective number of magi, the weaker their individual power.<br><br>Magic is the highest class of <a data-href="Mystery" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/mystery.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Mystery</a> that surpasses magecraft and all current sciences of that age. It represents the actualization of events that are impossible to reproduce in a certain era, whether by humans or the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Gaia" data-href="Gaia" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/gaia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Planet</a>, even if given an infinite amount of time and resources. It is is considered the ultimate accomplishment of a magus, and only within the grasp of those who have accessed the Root.<br>The difference between Magic and Magecraft is that Magic is truly Impossible an actual Miracle. But the Resurrection of the dead through conventional methods is something that not even Magic has granted since <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Gaia" data-href="Gaia" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/gaia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Age of Gods</a>.<br>Those who practice Magic are known as&nbsp;Magicians hey have control over their own Mysteries, but also practice magecraft. There are currently 5 Magics and two "living" magicians with a total of 4 in history.<br><br>It is still debatable whether Zelretch is alive or not but most believe he is.<br><br>Ouf ok this part is long sorry.<br>Magic Circuits are a pseudo-nervous system that spreads itself through the human body and what qualifies a person to be a magus.<br>They reside within the magus’&nbsp;soul and what is found on the body is just a physical expression of them that stretches itself throughout the body in a fashion similar to the nervous system. Magic Circuits do not change, and once damaged, they cannot be repaired.<br>
Their&nbsp;Quality and&nbsp;Quantity&nbsp;are&nbsp;ranked&nbsp;through letters (D rank to A kinda) and their&nbsp;Composition that describes the overall ability, often varies between magi.<br>Quality has to do with how powerful of a magecraft you can handle with your circuits.<br>
Quantity has to do with how many times you can perform this magecraft, and how large its scale is.<br>
Composition  has to do with the era of the "Mystery" they were created in.<br>The average Magus has about 20 magic circuits and can output up to 25 units of magical energy (The units act like spell slots in this case spells take a certain number units to cast).<br>the number of Magic Circuits that one possesses is determined at birth and cannot decrease or increase naturally, meaning that those from older lineages will be more powerful. It is possible to transplant Magic Circuits on another being but it is highly dangerous and there is a possibility of mutual destruction.<br><br>The Magic Circuits have two basic functions; one is to convert Life Force (Od) into magical energy and another is to access a cluster of&nbsp;Magic Formulae named the Thaumaturgical Foundations. <br>To explain this simply the Thaumaturgical Foundations refers to magical magical traditions, collections of rituals and spells that Modern Magi use. They were made in the past, and were so powerful that they were engraved on the world, and that is not bc people were better or something, they were just dumb and were like "dance and rain will fall n shit", but like Mystery was pretty strong back then, so that shit stuck. so you kinda need to follow a thaumaturgical Foundation from around the world, tho it is still possible to make formulae of your own just yk you're starting from scratch and Mystery has a terminal cancer going on rn.<br>Still, the Magic Circuits are ultimately something unnatural for the human body and their activity will cause pain and numbness to the magus as well as increase the bodily temperature of the user.<br>Magic Circuits are "opened" when magical energy is run through them for the first time. Based on their experience at that time, a magus makes their own mental trigger to activate their Magic Circuits at will from then on. For this reason, the triggers are different from each other and in an extreme case, self-injury can be regarded as a switch.<br>
So make a mental trigger for your masters, kinda just flavor but pretty cool.<br><br>Magical Energy is a source of energy found naturally within magi and the World, acting as the source to actualize the Mysteries of magecraft. It is the source that powers all forms of magecraft. Strictly speaking, mana and od are energy in its raw state, whereas magical energy is the name given to the energy once it is converted by the Magic Circuits.<br>Magical energy is primarily classified by two types, Mana and Od, separated only by whether it comes from the atmosphere or from within human magi. They are essentially identical in terms of quality, but the world's mana vastly exceeds humanity's od.<br>Mana is the "breath of the&nbsp;Planet&nbsp;filling the world and nature,"&nbsp;produced by the World&nbsp;through a network of&nbsp;Leylines across the globe. The density of mana on the planet is dependent on the age. Within the Age of Gods, the mana density is such that a modern human will die when exposed to it without any sort of protection.<br>
Magi freely utilize the mana in the air for the purpose of spells that exceed their personal   od, but the amount they can utilize at one time correlates to the capacity of their Magic Circuits.<br>
The mana within a given area is finite, Similar to magi needing time to regenerate their od, the mana of an area will take a long time to replenish after it is depleted.<br><br>Od is the&nbsp;life force energy found within living organisms such as humans, animals and Magical Beasts. Once depleted, the Magic Circuits that are stored in the human soul will begin to replenish it.<br>
Mana can be taken in accordingly with the capacities of the Magic Circuits,&nbsp;but the actual conversion process will take time.<br>
It is common practice among the magi to start up their spells with od and then keep them running with mana. Only small-scale spells that do not interact with the environment directly are performed entirely with od, an example of which would be reinforcement.<br>
Od is connected not only to a person's physical condition, but also to the characteristics carried by Blood.<br><br><br>Elements are the basic substances that shape the World and play an important role in magecraft. Depending on which teachings of magecraft one got(Kabbalah, Alchemy, etc...), one could classify everything of reality into different sets of Elements.<br>
The Five Great Elements are Fire, Water, Earth, Wind and Ether.<br>A magus is normally good at manipulating at least one of the Elements. To identify which of&nbsp;Five Great Elements his elemental affinity is, he can use&nbsp;Consecration, the method composed of the use of sage, tarot cards and personality tests.<br>
Some magi possesses more than one elemental affinity and sometimes use them at the same time. Those capable of manipulating all the five Elements receive the title of&nbsp;Average One: Wielder of Five Great Elements and are highly valued by the Mage’s Association.<br>
Elemental affinity only indicates what kind of magecrafts a magus is good at, not meaning he cannot at all use other Elements than his affinity.<br>
There are special cases where A magi's Affinity is equivalent to their Origin, for them magecrafts using any of the Five Great Elements are difficult to perform, ones with their unique Affinities in turn are so easy to handle that they can occasionally realize what is impossible with normal magecrafts. <br>&nbsp;<br>
(Make sure to choose what your Affinities for your Master as they may influence some abilities that will be given to them as the campaign progresses, Im giving you complete liberty to your choices though we might discuss on whether they are possible or not)<br>Known Elements
Fire&nbsp;
One of the Five Great Elements that has Warm and Dry features. It is well suited for destructive magecrafts, symbolizing life and death.&nbsp;In the Mage's Association, they call it normal
Magi who have Fire and Water, the opposite Element, as their affinities are few.
Earth&nbsp;
One of the Five Great Elements that has Cold and Dry features.
It is referred to as the essence of gemstones, when combined with Ether, the essence of magecraft, any other elements can be extracted from jewels.
Water
One of the Five Great Elements that has Cold and Wet features. Both this and Wind are good at liquid manipulation.
Wind&nbsp;
One of the Five Great Elements that has Warm and Wet features. In the Mage's Association, they call it noble&nbsp;probably because there are few number of users.
Void<br>
Also known as&nbsp;Ether, it is one of the Five Great Elements. Ether is also called the&nbsp;Fifth Imaginary Factor, according to the teachings of the Mage’s Association. It combines itself with any of the other four Elements in order to actualize then Mysteries of Magecraft. The successor to True Ether which died out after the Age of Gods.
Ether is the artificial magical energy that forms the basis of modern magecraft, although it did not exist during the Age of Gods.
Imaginary Numbers
Also called Hollow, it is an Imaginary Element that gives its users access to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The planes of Existence" data-href="The planes of Existence" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-planes-of-existence.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Imaginary Number Space</a>.
<br>Thaumaturgical Attribute also called&nbsp;Sorcery Trait, is one of the components that determines the effect of one's magecraft. I am not going to talk much about this one here but in <a data-href="Pf2e to Type Moon Conversion" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/pf2e-to-type-moon-conversion.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Pf2e to Type Moon Conversion</a>, but simply put these are the types of magic you can do like Reinforcement, Projection and Conversion.<br>Origin is the starting point that defines one's existence and directs one's actions throughout life. Coming from the Root it is the starting point that defines one's existence and directs one's actions throughout life. These actions are more along the lines of an inherent compulsion that could be called a person's instinct rather than a conscious decision. A creature's origin stays the same through all of its reincarnations. <br>The Origin can be awakened and if so it becomes impossible for a magus to stray from their Origin, an impulsive behavior one would follow as though it were an absolute order.<br>
For example if your origin was "to devour", you'd have impulses about eating things in your life "I wonder how that tastes like" and the like, but if it would be awakened, you would not be able to stop yourself from devouring, you'd devour all things whether you want it or not, and you'd like it.<br>Origins could be things like "Sword", "Freedom", "Nostalgia" and so on, and can be revealed through certain rituals.<br>Origins also may influence your Calling for the pf2e Mythic rules more on that in <a data-href="Pf2e to Type Moon Conversion" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/pf2e-to-type-moon-conversion.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Pf2e to Type Moon Conversion</a>.<br>(Your origin is not something you get to decide but something I will choose, though you can learn what it is and if you don't vibe with it Im always willing to hear ya out)<br><br>The equivalent to western magecraft across mainland continental Asia is called:<br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/magecraft.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Magecraft.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 16:41:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250210203937.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250210203937.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mystery]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>   Mystery is a sliver of power of many different types that comes from the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The planes of Existence" data-href="The planes of Existence" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-planes-of-existence.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Root</a>.<br>
It is the source of all supernatural phenomena such as&nbsp;<a data-href="Magecraft" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/magecraft.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magecraft</a>&nbsp;or&nbsp;<a data-href="Psychics" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/psychics.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Psychics</a>, and beings such as&nbsp;<a data-href="True Ancestors" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/true-ancestors.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">True Ancestors</a>, &nbsp;<a data-href="Dead Apostles" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/dead-apostles.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dead Apostles</a>,&nbsp;Servants,&nbsp;Spirits, as well as&nbsp;Phantasmal Species&nbsp;show signs of Mystery.&nbsp;Mystery accumulates over time and grows stronger with age.<br>  A Mystery thus holds meaning specifically because it is a mystery; if it were to be understood, it would lose that force. Magecraft is, in essence, Mystery. However, since the beginning of the Common Era, human history has been in the process of systematically erasing Mysteries. As the light of science expands, the darkness of Mystery recedes, &nbsp;No matter how&nbsp;magi&nbsp;resist this fact, this law remains unbent. Magecraft thus gets weaker when it's exposed, though what is meant by that is not the Magecraft of a particular individual, but all of Magecraft and in the future.<br>  Mystery hasn't degraded everywhere however. Compared to the surface, The <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The planes of Existence" data-href="The planes of Existence" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-planes-of-existence.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Texture of The Human World</a> influences the underground much less, so traces of Mystery still remain in the depths of the earth.<br>  In order to stave off the degradation of Mystery, <a data-href="The Mage's Association" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-mage's-association.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Mage's Association</a>&nbsp;was founded, and it began enforcing the&nbsp;Concealment of Mystery&nbsp; to preserve the strength of magecraft&nbsp;It was previously something of an unwritten law, but became enforced over time, with the popularization and vulgarization of Mysteries being tantamount to a crime in the&nbsp;World of Magecraft.<br>
   In 2007 Lord El-Melloi II estimates that the Concealment of Mystery won't last more than another five years, as they approach a time when anyone can upload high definition images to social networks in real time either new methods of secrecy will have to be devised, like seeding dummy stories and label everything fake news, or they will have to reveal something.
<br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.<br>
  Info known by higher positions or specific fields in The Mage's Association.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/mystery.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Mystery.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 16:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[<mark style="background: #CACFD9A6;"> </mark> Spiral Manor]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>The Spiral Manor is one of two major Magecraft organizations in China focused on the usage of <a data-href="Philosophy Magecraft" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/philosophy-magecraft.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Philosophy Magecraft</a>.<br>Also simply called the Manor, it is China's equivalent of the Mage's Association in the World of Magecraft. While the Clock Tower is the most powerful Magus organization in the world, the Spiral Manor may have more total members. The Spiral Manor's influence spreads across mainland Asia from China, to the Middle East in the west, and Singapore in the south. The Spiral Manor and Mage's Association have a feigned nonaggression pact with each other.<br><br>The Summit Court is the other major Magecraft organization in China focused on the usage of <a data-href="Philosophy Magecraft" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/philosophy-magecraft.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Philosophy Magecraft</a>.<br>Smaller than the Spiral Manor, the members of the Summit Court, the Ten Officials, are Xian from the Age of Gods.<br>
The Ten Officials created the Philosophy Foundation, they are presumed to be dead, missing, or inactive.<br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.<br>
May add more to these if I find more
]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/other-factions.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Other Factions.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:31:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pf2e to Type Moon Conversion]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Certain things in pathfinder 2e simply don't really work in the Nasuverse or need some more elaboration and adjustments to make work.<br>Thaumaturgical Attribute equivalent to Class for now. Generally, each magus' lineage is specialized in a certain Thaumaturgical Attribute. This is dependent on generations of research, and the types of Mysteries engraved in the Magic Crest. Which kinda means that if you were a magus, with like the fighter class (which I believe would be Reinforcement) your whole ancestors would've been the same class or at least something close to it.<br>
It is possible to acquire other Attributes tho (counted as archetypes in pf2e).<br>Since we are using Mythic rules, before the start of the Campaign I am going to need you to choose your <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://2e.aonprd.com/Rules.aspx?ID=3330" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link" href="https://2e.aonprd.com/Rules.aspx?ID=3330" target="_blank">Mythic Calling</a>. Now the part that is important here is your characters Origin, it may influence your Calling when your mythic powers awaken (Mythic rules will not be active from the start but will collectively take effect at some point in the Campaign).<br>
By influence I mean, it may add to your edicts and anathema, and also what exactly Mythic points can be used for. If your Origin is ever awakened one way or another it will override your edicts and anathema with NO OPTION TO REFUSE DOING THEM, so be careful.<br>Alright now for the things that can't be done:<br>
Resurrection spells in pf2e are nearly impossible to use in the World of Magecraft simply bc getting someone's soul out of Akasha is insane and would require something equivalent to Magic. For that reason, no resurrections will be allowed unless you started casting the spell the MOMENT the creature died.<br>
There are ways to mitigate this however, and that is only if you worked on the soul of the person that needs to be resurrected beforehand, only then will you be able to resurrect them. Now if you wish to do such a thing it will probably require some substantial effort to do during the campaign. (I will not add rules for how to do this unless someone wants to)<br>
Concepts like&nbsp;Time Manipulation, teleportation and spatial warping are also things magecraft can't do that are nearing Magic level of bs. So all effects in the domain of these 3 will not be possible unless:<br>
- Discussed during character creation.<br>
- Is done by Servants (since they technically are exceptions there is no need to limit this for them)<br>
- In regard to spatial warping, if one has The Imaginary Numbers Affinity they can use such abilities as written.<br>
This is not to say that you can't use any Abilities that have these thing, but more like it will need re-flavoring, you can still teleport but instead of it being actual teleportation, it is some sort of movement etc, same thing for Time manipulation, there are ways to re-contextualize such thing (Not to say that Time manipulation is impossible for a Master or anything but you get it). THE ONLY EXCEPTION IS SPATIAL WARPING, creating dimensional things like Forcecage (although the spell has completely changed in the remaster making it a wood trait thing, weird but that spell should be allowed now), or yeeting someone with Quandary is within the realms of The Imaginary Numbers and will need them.<br>
Once again Servants do not need to abide by these rules(Except for resurrection)<br><br>A Bounded Field is a geographical form of Magecraft whereby one knits a boundary line of Magical Energy around a space to separate its inside from the outside, cutting off and isolating that space from the outside world and then imposing an effect on the inside (or the boundary line itself). It is primarily used to protect one's body or property.<br>
When a Bounded Field is created,&nbsp;a spell slot must be expended (Or something equivalent), and several magic circles need to be spread around the area to keep it stable. At least&nbsp;1 magic circle&nbsp;needs to be created for&nbsp;each 100 feet&nbsp;within the Bounded Field.<br>The Bounded Field provides several benefits:

The Bounded Field isolates an area from the outside world, creating a separate space of its own. This creates an illusion that allows the mage to control how the inside view appears from the outside. Even creatures with abilities that let them see through illusions must&nbsp;attempt a check against the mage's spell DC. The Bounded Field is also under the effects of the&nbsp;Veil of Privacy spell, at a spell rank equal to that of the&nbsp;spell slot&nbsp;consumed when&nbsp;creating the Bounded Field.

The Bounded Field also protects the area from intruders. Unless permitted by the mage, no creature can enter the Bounded Field unless they succeed at&nbsp;a counteract check against the mage's spell DC.<br>
The check itself can be caused by anything the GM deems capable of bypassing or opening the Bounded Field, such as an Arcana check to try and disable part of the barrier, a Thievery check made by an expert in magical devices, or even an attack roll made by a magical weapon under the correct circumstances.<br>
All these different options may&nbsp;change the DC at the GM's discretion. Even effects that cover large areas do not affect the inside of a Bounded Field if they originate from the outside.<br>
Here are the results of the counteract check:<br>
Critical Success: You pass through the barrier or create an opening for your allies to go through&nbsp;without raising any suspicion.<br>
Success: You pass through the barrier or create an opening for your allies to go through, but whoever is inside&nbsp;the Bounded Field and its caster are made aware of the intrusion.<br>
Failure: You fail to break through the barrier, and whoever is inside the Bounded Field and its caster are made aware of the intrusion.<br>
Critical Failure: As failure,&nbsp;but you cannot attempt an intrusion with the same check for 1 minute.
<br>These are all the Rules I have made for now, more may be added and some changed (Though this completely depends on your feedback).]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/pf2e-to-type-moon-conversion.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Pf2e to Type Moon Conversion.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 21:48:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Philosophy Magecraft]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>  Philosophy Magecraft is just as wide and varied as&nbsp;Western Magecraft, the only things Philosophy Magecraft shares in common with the western magecraft are the barest fundamentals and the use of Magic circuits.<br>
  Philosophy Magecraft uses the&nbsp;Philosophy Foundation which is essentially a simulation of an artificial Root. It is also called&nbsp;The Disc, and was created by <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Other Factions" data-href="Other Factions" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/other-factions.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Summit Court</a> during the Age of Gods. The Xian (Humans who became powerful incarnated Elementals like True Ancestors) created their magecraft system by building a Supergiant Mystic Code that is fused with the planet. That is the Philosophy Foundation.<br>  This Philosophy foundation is the main difference between western and eastern magecraft, it is like a library that can be accessed using a combination of magic formulae and Philosophy Keys.<br>
  Philosophy keys are the counterpart to Magic crests and are also inherited as from master to student. The higher the class of the Philosophy key the more of the library one can access. <br>  The changes to magecraft at the end of the Age of Gods reached everyone equally, including Philosophy Magecraft, and that brought about major losses and minor benefits. It's possible to access the Philosophy Foundation without a Key, but the usable magecraft is limited to the basic spells<br>  The goal of Philosophy Magecraft is not to reach the Root, but rather to make the Philosophy Foundation match the Root's accuracy, although that act is akin to attempting to fix a long-broken plate without having all the missing parts.<br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/philosophy-magecraft.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Philosophy Magecraft.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:28:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Psychics]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>  A&nbsp;Psychic refers to one who has&nbsp;a mutation, an&nbsp;Abnormal Ability gained as a result of the brain being able to comprehend a "channel" (common sense, or perception of reality) not native to humans. It is a different type of <a data-href="Mystery" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/mystery.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Mystery</a> than <a data-href="Magecraft" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/magecraft.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magecraft</a>, although similar in nature.<br>  Psychic Power, also referred to as&nbsp;Extrasensory Perception&nbsp;(ESP), is a catch-all term to refer to the circuits that cause supernatural phenomena to occur. Unlike&nbsp;magecraft, which can be taught and practiced, inherent ability is an absolute necessity. Psychic Powers are the ultimate ability of&nbsp;humans, who have become an existence independent of nature.<br>  They only appear by chance (for example, they can be the result of an accident causing a permanent change in the brain),&nbsp;and are limited to one generation,  although it is possible to force them to become a genetic trait carried by blood.<br>
  Generally Psychics still have both the normal "channel", the perception all human beings have, and their abnormal "channel". However, there rarely exist those who only possess the latter who cannot live within society's rules of common sense, These are known as&nbsp;Unfit Existences and tend to go crazy.<br>
  There are several powers Psychics can have such as Precognition and Retrocognition but the most known cases are Mystic Eyes.<br><br>  Mystic Eyes are a form of supernatural power concentrated in the eyes, granting the power to interfere with the outer world through sight alone. They are the oldest magecraft known to humans, deriving from neither ritual nor study.<br>
Mystic Eyes usually work like Single Action spells and are activated through the use of magical energy. Since they have their own Magic Circuits, Mystic Eyes are able to produce magical energy and cast spells all on their own. <br>  It is possible to suppress the power of Mystic Eyes with a Mystic Code called Mystic Eye Killers. They are commonly made into glasses because Mystic Eyes are a power derived from the oculus.<br>  Within the Clock Tower, Mystic Eyes have their own system of ranking called Noble Color. Normal Mystic Eyes shine red or green, strong ones glow a luminous Gold, and Mystic Eyes that fall in the realm of Gods glimmer with multiple colors, like Jewels' or Rainbows.<br>
so the ranking goes: Rainbow &gt; Jewel &gt; Gold &gt; Red. The higher the rank the more rare they are, like Jewel and Rainbow ranks are so rare that their very existence is hypothetical and can't even be verified.<br>
"A Noble Color is like the movement of the stars compared to normal Magic Circuits" is a common saying in the World of Magecraft.<br><br>if one wants to gain true Mystic Eyes, there is no option to acquire a transplant except the&nbsp;Rail Zeppelin, the Mystic Eye Collection Train that runs through the forests of Europe, collecting any and all Mystic Eyes. Mystic Eyes are something developed and rooted within one's own body, so even removing them is incredibly difficult. But the Rail Zeppelin is an exception to that, ignoring all problems of physical rejection and the like, and not just extracting them, but capable of transplanting Mystic Eyes directly into a new host without risk of failure.<br>
The Rail Zeppelin also invites possessors of strong Mystic Eyes to come sell their eyes, under threat of being killed and having their Mystic Eyes ripped out if they do not comply.<br><br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.<br>
  Info known by higher positions or specific fields in The Mage's Association.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/psychics.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Psychics.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:01:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250211194122.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250211194122.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Atlas Institute]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>(My favorite faction in the whole verse tbh)<br>
  The Atlas Institute, sometimes abbreviated as Atlas and also known as the&nbsp;Titan's Pit, is one of the three major branches of the Mage's Association specialized in Alchemy. This organization is named after the&nbsp;Atlas Mountains (Big Morocco W) <br><br>  The magi in Atlas are expert Alchemists, an assembly of geniuses. For them, there are no taboos and no penalties to prevent the creation of the most unethical of weapons. Their only one rule is that things which are created here must never leave. That is the founding principle of the Atlas Temple. They fear people leaving more than they care about visitors. They are rare to act directly, and see other Magi organizations as foolish for taking actions that may lead to the extinction of mankind they are so dedicated to preventing. Unlike the Clock Tower, they have no interest in reaching the Root, with their research being entirely dedicated to preventing the doomsday scenarios they predict.<br>  The often spoke-up "transformation of base metal to gold" in Alchemy is, to the members of the Atlas Temple, mere "transformation of matter" and is nothing more than a primitive art far removed from their ideals. Most of them  cannot perform Magecraft of great power due to the lack of&nbsp;Magic Circuits.<br>  «&nbsp;We have no need to be the strongest. We create that which is the strongest.&nbsp;»<br>
This is a central dogma of the Atlas Temple’s alchemists.<br><br>The&nbsp;Contracts of Atlas&nbsp;are seven contracts issued as of the founding of Atlas. They leave Atlas bound to cooperation with those in possession of one of the contracts at their demand.&nbsp;The recovery of these contracts is a goal of Atlas. As of the year 2000, four contracts had been recovered, but the locations of the *remaining three were unknown*.<br><br>The process the Alchemists of Atlas use to study Mysteries does not depend on Magical Energy. Instead, they relied on a great many tools. Atlas' development was similar to the progress of science and technology.<br>Following this principle, Atlas has birthed a great arsenal of weapons. In order to avoid the "end" proven by their first director, they endlessly create and dispose of weapon after weapon. The reason being that the weapons created there to save the world are ultimately nothing more than tools that will further its destruction.<br>The&nbsp;Seven Superweapons of Atlas are seven weapons on display at Atlas. Each Superweapon was created to save humanity, but also has the potential to destroy it. There is a saying in the Prague Association (A smaller alchemist group of the mages association): "Lift not the seal of Atlas, lest ye destroy the world seven times over."<br>The&nbsp;TRI-HERMES: The Pseudo-Spiritronic Processor are Atlas Temple’s greatest storage media, in the form of obelisks. All events are recorded in TRI-HERMES, it is a supercomputer completed using Spiritons (magic soul particle wumbo jumbo. Im not explaining this, you don't need it. thx).<br><br>Called The Atlas Temple, It is located somewhere among the mountains of Egypt. It is an underground academy full of Mysteries. The Alchemists each have their own independent&nbsp;Workshops, within which they conduct their research. Laboratories built with unknown technologies.<br>There are storehouse for Mystic Codes, though they are considered to be no more than a junkyard. The Atlas Alchemists invented many devices, deemed them failures, and dumped them into a terrifying mountain of weapons.<br>In the center of the academy, it is where TRI-HERMES is located. The core of Atlas has a man-made sky in this underground chamber.<br><br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.<br>
  Info known by higher positions or specific fields in The Mage's Association.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-atlas-institute.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Atlas Institute.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:12:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250212200349.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250212200349.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Church]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>  The Holy Church, also referred simply as the Church, is the hidden side of the Roman Catholic Church that specializes in the hunting of heresy.<br>
Compared to the public side of the Holy Church that treats heresies as if they do not exist because those who teach the word of God must not acknowledge that which runs counter to their doctrines. The Holy Church contains the zealots who feel the heresies should be more proactively destroyed. They are a major force that has a tenuous relationship with <a data-href="The Mage's Association" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-mage's-association.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Mage's Association</a>.<br><br>  Those who insult God, kill people, mislead the public, and twist the very&nbsp;Laws of Nature&nbsp;by occult means fall under the umbrella of “heretics” and are targets for the Church’s forces.<br>
The Holy Church are one of the very few organizations larger in scale than <a data-href="The Clock Tower" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-clock-tower.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Clock Tower</a><br>
They are the largest organization in the World of Magecraft.<br>
While being a religious organization, the Holy Church is dedicated to "protecting the works of man in the name of the Lord", fighting to protect human society even in nations where most of the population does not follow the Christian religion<br>  While the Association seeks to conceal Mystery from the public and preserve it, the Church attempts to “properly manage” it, destroying any Mysteries they deem as heresy. While the Church generally abides by the policy of concealing Mystery that the Association enforces, It does not really care. Some of the magecraft it employs, namely the Baptism Rites are basically public. However they have been covert even before the Association chose to conceal magecraft about their Anti-Vampire Activities.<br>  While the Holy Church has spent most of its history in open and violent conflict with the Mage's Association, in recent years the organizations have come to a truce, forming a non-aggression pact.<br>&nbsp;  ‌the‌ members of the Church‌ ‌share‌ ‌a‌ ‌common‌ ‌ideology.‌ ‌The‌ ‌singular bond of faith puts the Church above‌ ‌the constant ‌infighting‌ ‌and‌ ‌atmosphere of mutual‌ ‌distrust‌ found in the‌ ‌Association.‌ ‌While ‌Church’s‌ ‌members‌ disagree on and ‌debate‌ ‌their‌ differing ‌interpretations‌ ‌of‌ ‌doctrine,‌ this amounts to nothing more than reasonable discussions (Crazy I know) on how to become better people.<br>  the&nbsp;Church's Teachings and Holy Words, is the most widespread and well stabilized Thaumaturgical Foundation in the&nbsp;World. It makes possible the use of Sacraments.<br>
In the Holy Church, it is considered taboo to use the terminology preferred by magi due to the organization’s long-standing conflict with the Mage’s Association. Members of the Church therefore refer to magical energy as "holy energy", and so Sacraments are simply a blanket statement that encompasses all Magecraft they use.<br>
Officially the Church does not even teach any spells but the&nbsp;Baptism Rite.<br><br><br>The&nbsp;Assembly of the Eighth Sacrament is a special agency made up of a group of special clerics charged with the research, recovery, and managing of holy relics scattered across the globe. The members follow the "Eighth Sacrament" outside of the&nbsp;Sacraments of the Catholic Church, the seven graces that God bestowed: Baptism, Holy Eucharist, Matrimony, Holy Orders, Confirmation, Penance, Anointing. It is a "power separated from the faith", meaning the members trained to retrieve the hidden relics do not fear being involved in heretical power such as magecraft to accomplish their goals.<br><br>The&nbsp;Executors&nbsp;are the heretic inquisitors of the Holy Church established by the 120th Cardinal. They have the task of&nbsp;demon killing and the destruction of other heretical beings.<br>It is known as the bloodiest department of the Church, called the Shura's Den for its responsibility of punishing heresies. It takes a certain amount of willpower to be part of it, and being able to achieve the title of "Executor" signifies that one is a first-rate murderer that has passed brutal and pious training to become mankind's weapon.<br>
One of the ironclad rules of the Holy Church is that Executors operating in the field are granted complete independent authority to resolve the incident until their task is complete, and not even someone at the top of the organization’s hierarchy have the authority to interfere with them while they are under this protection. Despite this high degree of autonomy, the Executors are of low rank in the Church’s hierarchy. They are disposable soldiers who exist to fight and die on the battlefield.<br>The Executors also follow the&nbsp;"Eighth Sacrament" granting the permit to stray away from the rules of their religion as long as one thing, the name of the Almighty, is protected. They are followers that do not teach the words of the Lord, but act as His representative, His Executors, despite being mere mortals.<br><br><br>The Burial Agency is a group of special Inquisitors gathered by the Holy Church. A secret division of the Holy Church, an organization of Europe's prominent religion whose name means "universal".<br>It comprises seven Executors. A walking Armory; a security force consisting of a mere handful of people. They are in charge of exterminating the "inhuman things" that never show themselves, which the Church condemned as heresies — <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dead Apostles" data-href="Dead Apostles" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/dead-apostles.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Vampires</a>.<br>When it comes to the Executors of the Burial Agency, they will stop at nothing if it's to apprehend a&nbsp;Dead Apostle, even having a whole town disappear from the map. They have the authority where whatever they do is allowed if their opponent is a vampire, and that includes the city targeted by the Dead Apostle: whether humans still live there or not, if it's an already defiled land, they will burn it down all the same. For the Burial Agency, being a non-human Prime Species&nbsp;is on its own "evil".<br>
"Prime Species" refers simply to a world's dominant species, and does not necessarily imply the intelligence to form civilization.<br>There is an eighth reserve member, but they are not granted the same privilege. The privilege of independent action permitted by the Archbishop are the 7 members only, therefore it was decided that adding more than that would be dangerous.<br><br>The&nbsp;Chivalric Orders&nbsp;are the&nbsp;Knights that make up the main military body of each church. They only fight to defend holy ground. They are known for using halberds, but the weapon's popularity is dying out among them.<br>
Some Knights of the Chivalric Orders are also involved in training Executors.<br><br>Exorcists are a special kind of priests charged as "representatives" by the bishop of a diocese. They are a type of Executor not geared for heretic hunting, but rather answer pleas for help and visit those towns to exorcise Daemons (not to be confused with  demons) using their Baptism Rite.<br>While the mere likes of humans are no match for a mature Daemon, the real problem for the visiting Exorcists is the protection of the&nbsp;soul. The experience of Daemon exorcism is said to be one that a person cannot withstand more than once, making an iron faith more sought after than physical prowess. The Exorcists don't fear Daemons, but rather they fear the breaking of their will. There is only one known account of a mature Daemon being exorcised. <br><br>The&nbsp;Order of the Templars s a small but powerful faction in the Church. Although they have a considerable amount of connections and allegiance to the Church, the Order of the Templars is often not part of the Church. They are in truth a separate independent organization of their own and hold only loyalty to themselves.<br>The Templars are considered to be far more radical, bordering the line of terrorism in their activities, as they hire criminals to work for them or even join their ranks. They seem to specialize in heretic hunting and often lend some of their own Heretic Hunters to the Holy Church, when necessary.<br><br><br>Wraith, also referred to as Ghosts or Human Spirits, are souls of dead people that remain attached to this world due to past grudges, regrets and other sorts of unfinished business that they had during life. However, as they are no longer something that belongs to this world, their existence is something that degrades with time and they are bound to disappear eventually.<br>Normally, direct physical interference on the part of these Ghosts are low. As Spiritual Bodies they usually have to act through some sort of medium. <br>As Human Spirits they are able to consume the&nbsp;souls&nbsp;and minds of people and convert them into energy. The basic abilities they had from the time when they where alive still remain but they don't change from such nourishment, as they only become tougher as their&nbsp;Magical Energy&nbsp;capacity increases.<br><br>Demons are existences that, while being of the&nbsp;Laws of Nature, disturb its flow. The distortion that these cause to their surroundings is rather high, requiring them to be put down.<br><br>The&nbsp;Sixth Imaginary Factor also known as Daemons, is a force that reacts to the desires of humans and births Daemons out of their wishes. It needs a form, invented by humans, in order to materialize itself as a passive existence. This passive existence is an individual Daemon and not a True Daemon.<br>
But regardless of the result, as a rule, Daemons are gentle. They are the Imaginary Factor that understands one's pain and attempts to remove it. Depending on perspective, one can say that they are allies of humanity. They act to realize the wishes they come to be invested within by distorted means.<br>In general, a Daemon usually takes possession of the human that birthed it. But in the event that the mind of the host cannot withstand the strain, it is common for the self-destruction of the host to occur, dispersing the essence of the Daemon into the vicinity. Upon possession by a daemon, irregularities manifest in the the victim's body, eventually rendering them as grotesque monsters by the metamorphosis of the flesh, once this process is complete they become a mature Daemon.<br>Daemons need something called a Unit Designation to be free, while True Daemons don't, what does that mean? what are true daemons exactly? idk, this is not something very well explored in the nasuverse all we know is True Daemons strong a fuckload.<br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.<br>
  Info known by higher positions or specific fields in The Mage's Association.<br>
  Info known by people of the church.<br>
  Info known by Specific divisions of the church of the Church.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-church.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Church.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:25:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250212225143.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250212225143.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Clock Tower]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>  The Clock Tower is the first branch and headquarters of the Mage's Association, officially formed as of 500 AD, it is located in London, in the United Kingdom of Great Britain.<br><br>  The Clock Tower is currently under the control of a pseudo-aristocratic elite called the Lords. Each Lord holds great political power within the Association just by himself.<br>  Preconceived and discriminatory behavior is somewhat widespread inside the Clock Tower. The Enforcers are looked down upon by the upper ranks. Discrimination against Asians is common, which might be a factor on why so few of them are members of the Association.<br>  Admission of new members involves exams to test one's knowledge of Magecraft, but it is possible to bypass this and become a scholarship student through letters of recommendation or the successor of a distinct lineage of Magi, having outstanding talent or even by accomplishing an impressive display of Magecraft.<br><br>The Lords: Noble are the three major families that hold sway over the Clock Tower, Barthomeloi, Trambelio, and Valualeta, and around twenty families of relatives. They are objects of fear within the Clock Tower, and they are even well-known in normal society. These families are what established the Three main factions of the clock Tower:<br>Aristocratic Faction&nbsp;<br>
<br>Leading family:&nbsp;Barthomeloi&nbsp;Faction.
<br>Purpose: They believe the management of the Clock Tower should be handed to those nobility who had proven to have excellent bloodlines.
<br>Democratic Faction&nbsp;<br>
<br>Leading family:&nbsp;Trambelio&nbsp;Faction.
<br>Supporting factions: Valualeta Faction.
<br>Purpose: They believe bloodline should be disregarded and those with the talent should be in charge.<br>
Neutral Faction&nbsp;
<br>Leading family:&nbsp;Meluastea&nbsp;Faction. (these guys are just chilling)
<br>Purpose: They don't care one way or the other, and just want to do their research in peace.
<br><br>The Clock Tower divides the city of London based on faculty and department, divided into 12 domains of mysticism. The architecture varies depending on the district, the city reflecting the specialties of each faculty. The main school is in London, consisting of Mystile, the Faculty of General Fundamentals. The Twelve Faculties are ruled by the Twelve Lords.<br><br>The majority of the Magi begin their studies at General Fundamentals for four or five years, and then move on to other Faculties, usually entering the Faculty associated with their lineage.<br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-clock-tower.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Clock Tower.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:09:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250212185531.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250212185531.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Counter Force]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>    The&nbsp;Counter Force&nbsp;is a safety device employed by Gaia or Alaya&nbsp;to defend itself against extinction. The Counter Forces are described as passive spirals of energy that respond to threats of planet destruction or human extinction. Usually, the Counter Forces act indirectly constantly steering mankind and the planet away from potential danger.<br>Although Gaia and Alaya are intangible forces of will, each does enlist physical agents to deal with events too threatening to address with indirect intervention.<br>
The agents of Gaia consist of the Elementals such as: *Fairies, <a data-href="True Ancestors" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/true-ancestors.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">True Ancestors</a>, some Phantasmal Species**, and some Divine Spirits.<br>
The agents of Alaya are Heroic Spirits, the Counter Guardians, human Spirits who pledge their eternal service to Alaya in return for power during their lifetime.<br><br>Counter Guardians, also called the&nbsp;Protectors of Balance**, is a broad classification of Heroic Spirits made up of heroes who are not worshipped, utilized as a mindless machines. Certain Heroic Spirits have a high&nbsp;Divinity&nbsp;and act as existences closer to the planet than humanity, so they are able to avoid being drafted by the Counter Force.<br>Normal circumstances are those where the Counter Force empowers a "normal person" in life to remove a factor that can trigger destruction, eventually causing them to be worshipped as heroes. Those who become heroes in such a manner are then used as Counter Guardians after they die.<br><br><br>  Parallel Worlds refers to divergent timelines that advance in adjacence to one another.<br>    The primary history of the worlds is called the&nbsp;Proper Human History, consisting of all worlds that have not been&nbsp;pruned. Worlds that have been cut off from Proper Human History in this way are known as&nbsp;Lostbelts. This is the Ultimate Defense of the Counter Force, certain divergent timelines wherein the&nbsp;"Foundation", of either Humanity or The World, is sufficiently deviant that its civilization no longer resembles those within the timelines of the Primary Branch, are culled and discarded from the Tree.<br>
When such a thing happens those worlds are left with no Counter Force protecting them and soon fall into annihilation.<br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.<br>
  Info known by higher positions or specific fields in The Mage's Association.<br>
  Info known by Specific divisions of the church of the Church]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-counter-force.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Counter Force.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 16:55:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/archer_shirou_emiya&apos;s_contract.webp" length="0" type="image/webp"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/archer_shirou_emiya&apos;s_contract.webp&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Holy Grail War]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Murder Death Kill Game, The Holy Grail War, I don't really  need to explain what it is, yk the deal, 7 masters, 7 servants battle Royal. A least that's what it's supposed to be.<br>  Established in Fuyuki Japan during the 1800s, throughout all 5 Holy grail wars in that city, the magical community at large has grown to know of it as a competition to win a&nbsp;Holy Grail.<br>  The Holy Grail's true nature is a gate to reach <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The planes of Existence" data-href="The planes of Existence" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-planes-of-existence.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Root</a>, However, the ritual's very premise is flawed: Only a Spiritual Body&nbsp;like a Servant, not a flesh-and-blood Master, is capable of grasping the Grail and completing the ritual. As such, the final Master, instead of sacrificing their own Servant to perfect the Grail and reach the Root, must keep their Servant alive to claim an energy source that is much weaker, but still capable of granting far-reaching wishes to the final Master/Servant pair. <br>  Overall, the Fuyuki Holy Grail War is a minor event in the&nbsp;World of Magecraft. As a conflict between Magi, the wars' preparation and decision-making are controlled by the&nbsp;Mage's Association. To avoid conflicts of interest, the Associate invites the&nbsp;Holy Church&nbsp;as Arbiters to onboard new Masters and neutrally enforce rules. While many people may perish in the Holy Grail War rituals, the Association only seeks to make sure the media is properly manipulated as to avoid letting it become public. The&nbsp;Fifth Holy Grail War took place in 2004.<br><br>  The were also the True and False Holy Grail Wars Of America in 2009, organized by The American Government. For unknown reason not much information is left from that event.<br><br>Heroic Spirits are Spirits of heroes who achieved great deeds in life, having become objects of worship after their deaths.<br>Heroic Spirits are beings of a higher existence, becoming categorically closer to&nbsp;Elementals&nbsp;than&nbsp;Wraiths. Differing from how Elementals are "power" granted form using human imagination as a container, they are entirely woven from the ideals of people all throughout and so can be greatly influenced by that vision when summoned.<br>Heroic Spirits are made up of those who truly existed, those only from legends, and those who were never observed at all.&nbsp;Those who existed had belief of their deeds gathered upon their deaths and were sublimated into beings of higher rank, while those who only existed in myths and legends were born from the gathering of those beliefs even if they didn't exist. Those who were not observed are those who made a contract of some sort with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Counter Force" data-href="The Counter Force" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-counter-force.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Alaya</a> during their lives and subsequently became Heroic Spirits and Counter Guardians respectively after their deaths as compensation.<br>Only the World itself can summon the "main body" of Heroic Spirits, so humans can only summon emanations of the heroes, such as through the&nbsp;Servant system. The souls of the emanations, their information, then returns to the main body upon the death of the emanation, and the main body is able to know about the actions of the emanations as records, as if they are reading books.<br>As beings outside of time, they can be summoned to any era regardless of the notions of past and future, even if summoned to when their human selves have yet to die or when they have yet to be born. The Holy Grail then grants them the necessary information to operate and understand the Era they have been summoned into.<br><br>Gods were beings formed by the thoughts of Humans and born into the world without being influenced by the will of the people. They grow stronger the more people worship them, but have been reduced to Divine Spirits since the end of the Age of Gods.<br>
Divine Spirits are much stronger than your average Heroic Spirit although since they are not part of the Throne of Heroes they have never been summoned in a Holy Grail War.<br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-holy-grail-war.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Holy Grail War.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 18:17:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250214202020.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250214202020.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Mage's Association]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>  The Mage's Association is an international, self-preservative and self-defense organization formed by magi for the purpose of controlling, concealing, and developing magecraft.<br>  Although the emphasis lies on the pursuit of knowledge, the Mage's Association also seeks to increase its own military strength and reserves the use of force to protect itself from entities that threaten its existence, such as <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Church" data-href="The Church" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-church.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Holy Church</a>, other magi organizations, supernatural forces seeking to punish mankind for meddling with areas that should not be touched, and individuals who hunt that which they consider taboo<br>  Perhaps out of pragmatism, the Association forbids the criminal use of magecraft.&nbsp;It does not allow research that would harm society or involve innocents.&nbsp;If a magus pulls a civilian into a magical phenomenon, the Association dispatch assassins to kill that magus.<br>  The Mage's Association was formed around 0 AD by a group of remaining magi from the Age of Gods, among which were Brishisan and Kischur Zelretch Schweinorg, in order to preserve its knowledge. As True Ether was replaced by Ether in 20 AD, the magi who chose to go forward with modern magecraft and Mystery chose to continue with the main Association, but those who refused the new magecraft decided to close themselves off in Atlas and the Wandering Sea.<br>The Mage's Association is divided into three main branches:<br>
<br><a data-href="The Clock Tower" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-clock-tower.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Clock Tower</a>
<br><a data-href="The Atlas Institute" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-atlas-institute.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Atlas Institute</a>
<br>  <a data-href="The Wandering Sea" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-wandering-sea.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Wandering Sea</a>
<br>  As long as he/she does not possess a Sealing Designation, a magus may leave the Association at any time without facing any restrictions. However, this is rarely done, since the Association provides its members with a great amount of resources, stored knowledge and other benefits. But if one would depart the World of Magecraft entirely, they are considered traitors and enemies of magi, and hunted down by the organization.<br>  Whenever there are issues concerning Magic, Zelretch appears before the Association and delivers fair and just judgment.<br><br>The Mage's Association and the&nbsp;Holy Church have a non-aggression agreement between each other for quite a while now, but armed conflict still tends to happen often in an off-the-records fashion.<br>
The Mage's Association has an antagonistic relationship with&nbsp;America&nbsp;and the country's Magi, and its influence isn't strong in Russia.<br><br>Sealing Designations are edicts handed down by the Mage's Association to maintain and protect special thaumaturgical abilities which cannot be acquired through study. Said to be a title of the "greatest honor", those marked are deemed "precious", causing the Association to mobilize the greatest effort to secure their flesh and blood, their body's potential.<br>Those Designated are to be incarcerated, becoming samples preserved in their present conditions and levels of ability. Genuine Sealing Designations are extremely rare, and those who pursue them, Enforcers, will be lucky to pursue even one in an entire decade.<br><br>Sealing Designation Enforcer, also known as Enforcers, are magi specialized in hunting down magi marked with Sealing Designations. Though there are said to be around thirty official Enforcers, Freelancers also hunt such people for a bounty placed by the Mage's Association.<br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.<br>
  Info known by higher positions or specific fields in The Mage's Association.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-mage&apos;s-association.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Mage&apos;s Association.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:13:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Magi]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20250212002153.png" src="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250212002153.png"><br>  Magus is the term for a practitioner of magecraft, the magical science. Magi frequently, but not necessarily, descend from old magical families, as affinity to magecraft is something transmitted through blood relations.<br>  More than just a name, the term "magus" defines a whole set of beliefs and lifestyle, the first of which is the desire to reach the "Root". No matter the cost, they use all their assets and abilities to reach that goal, and any abilities gained in the process are a by-product. They hold no meaning except as a means to reach the Truth.<br>
  A magus searches for the greater truths of the universe not to answer existential questions, but just for the sake of knowing. If something cannot be achieved with modern magecraft, the magi research and develop their magecraft just for the sake of changing that. Powerful magecrafts like&nbsp;Grand Magecraft&nbsp; and&nbsp;Grand Rituals are ultimately challenges in order to reach the goal called <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Magecraft" data-href="Magecraft" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/magecraft.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a>.<br>It is also standard amongst magi to make up for every deed, item or piece of information given to them with repayment of equal value.<br>
Ideally, a magus would render his own self transparent while still retaining his ego. In   reality, however, most magi, especially those of the Mage's Association, are often caught up in petty power struggles.<br>  One rule among magi is that it is taboo to kill your own students, because it goes against a magus' instinct of passing on their hopes to reach the&nbsp;Root&nbsp;on the next generation Since students and apprentices are like their own offspring and they are like their parents, magi fight fiercely to protect them, no matter what.<br>  Freelancer<br>
A magus who is not affiliated to any magical organizations and takes up jobs from others in exchange for remuneration. Due to the nature of their profession, they are constantly at odds with the Enforcers of the Mage's Association and the Executors of the Holy Church. Aoko Aozaki / Blue is probably the most well known Freelancer but she is simply strong enough that not many can oppose her.<br><br>Magic Crests are the most important treasure of a lineage of magi. Engraved on the body in a variety of shapes, most typically in a magic circle, a Magic Crest is a series of Magic Circuits that were given a more stable form in order to act as an archive of magecraft.<br>At some point of the magus’ life, he will forge some of his own Magic Circuits into the Magic Crest, store many, if not all,&nbsp;spells&nbsp;that he learned in life and then pass it down to his successor. As the process repeats itself with each new generation, the older a lineage is, the greater the number of Magic Circuits forming the Magic Crest, and the greater the amount of knowledge stored inside it. <br>As long as the Magic Crest is completely integrated with the magus' body, he will be able to cast any spell recorded in the Magic Crest, even if he himself never had the chance to learn it properly.<br>&nbsp;the Magic Crest is still a highly valued article for any magus. But since usually only one person can inherit it, troubles can arise when there is more than one candidate. It’s not unheard of for bloody feuds to erupt within a clan of magi because of a dispute between two or more children fighting over the family’s Magic Crest. It was because of that and other reasons that the current trend of only one heir per family (and the consequential policy of forsaking or excluding all other children) came to be.<br><br>The name given to those who use magecraft without following the way of the magus, those who treat magecraft as just a tool. Usually, their general skill with magecraft is low, but it is not uncommon for them to be highly proficient in a single field that they choose to specialize at. Also includes magi who lack formal training.<br><br>A Mystic Code: Magic Formal Wear or simply Formal Wear, is a tool that magi use to support their execution of magecraft. to put it simply it is the way Magus call Magic items. (During the campaign we will refer to magic items as mystic codes )<br><br>The magical laboratory of a Magus where he performs his researches and experiments. During its construction, the most important procedure is to prevent the&nbsp;magical energy&nbsp;inside of the Workshop from leaking out so its presence can be concealed.<br>
Magi usually set up&nbsp;Bounded Fields around their Workshops to protect them. Stepping into the Workshop of a Magus without his permission is seen as an act of open hostility.<br>Bounded Fields will be talked more in <a data-href="Pf2e to Type Moon Conversion" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/pf2e-to-type-moon-conversion.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Pf2e to Type Moon Conversion</a> and will use the same rules as Caster.<br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-magi.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Magi.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:03:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250212002153.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250212002153.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The planes of Existence]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>&nbsp;<br><br>Literally the world, but not to be confused with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Gaia" data-href="Gaia" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/gaia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The World</a>. Not much to say about it except that it's a Texture, a Layer of the fabric of reality that with several other layers make up the surface of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Gaia" data-href="Gaia" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/gaia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The World</a> <br><br><br>It is the&nbsp;layer&nbsp;of the&nbsp;World&nbsp;that retains the laws of the Age of the Gods, housing surviving&nbsp;Phantasmal species&nbsp;instead of people. Also known as the&nbsp;Inner Sea of the Planet or the&nbsp;D-Layer&nbsp;it is the place where the&nbsp;soul of the World&nbsp;is kept.<br>It is the bottom Texture or Layer of the World located 2700 kilometers below the surface (digging won't get you there unless you can rip space-time), it is akin to several Reality Marbles merged together all representing a facet of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Gaia" data-href="Gaia" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/gaia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The World</a>.<br>The Reverse Side of the World is a legendary, otherworldly paradise that cannot be reached by normal ways, spoken of in many cultures around the world as a land of immortality. It has had many names throughout history, including Utopia, the&nbsp;Garden of Eden ,&nbsp;Tír na nÓg, and&nbsp;Avalon.<br>It is not easy to reach the reverse side, you normally need very powerful magic, or just coincidence, or being dragged there, also not having a body is advisable due to the nature of the reverse side.<br>
<img alt="Pasted image 20250204114027.png" src="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250204114027.png"><br><br>Swirl of the Root also known as The Root or The Akashic Records (simply Akasha) &nbsp;is a metaphysical location that acts as the "force" that exists at the top of all theories in every dimension, as well as the source of all events and phenomena in the universe.<br>the "Outside of the World," as opposed to the&nbsp;World and its&nbsp;Reverse Side. Existing outside of time, it stores and archives information of all possibilities and events, past, present, and future, of the world. It is the place from where all&nbsp;souls including those of&nbsp;Heroic Spirits&nbsp;recorded on the&nbsp;Throne of Heroes, originate from and to where they return after death, before being reincarnated into something else.<br>Reaching The Root is one of the most difficult feats to achieve, the methods used to reach it usually involve reaching the pinnacle of a certain "concept". Those who have touched it directly have never returned to the world. <br>
<br>As it has no connection to this actual world, the&nbsp;Holy Church, which is only interested in this world, finds it completely meaningless.
<br><br><br>  Also occasionally referred to as the&nbsp;Ring of Deterrence a place existing outside of both the&nbsp;World&nbsp;and the time axis. It is where<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Holy Grail War" data-href="The Holy Grail War" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-holy-grail-war.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Heroic Spirits</a> and divine spirits are stored.<br>  It is implied by several events in FGO that although the throne exists outside of time and space, it has a space an time of its own as several servants have done things or met others in The throne. (This info is completely irrelevant to the campaign as your servant comes in blank memory of the throne but it is weirdly funny)<br>
<img alt="Pasted image 20250205212408.png" src="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250205212408.png"><br><br>The Imaginary number space, the "anti-reality" is an alternative space within the Reverse Side of the World from which the&nbsp;<a data-href="Magecraft" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/magecraft.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magecraft</a>&nbsp;concept of&nbsp;Imaginary Numbers&nbsp;originates. It is&nbsp;an unobservable territory, undetectable by the current laws of physics. It contains all possibilities due to being unobserved, though for that same reason nothing actually exists within it. <br>It is not normally hostile to normal reality, which are known as "Real Numbers", but if the Imaginary Numbers were made observable (without any quantum shenanigans), then they could become lethal to normal life and the interaction between Real Numbers and Imaginary Numbers becoming observable to each other can cause insanity.<br><img alt="Pasted image 20250205211812.png" src="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250205211812.png"><br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.<br>
  Nobody knows this.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-planes-of-existence.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The planes of Existence.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 16:37:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250205180512.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250205180512.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Wandering Sea]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>  The&nbsp;Wandering Sea also known as Baldanders, is the third branch of the Mage's Association.<br>
  The Wandering Sea is the original foundation of the Mage's Association that was formed long before the Clock Tower. In 20 AD, those Magi of Atlas and the Wandering Sea disagreed with the third faction led by the Association Director Brishisan, that would later become the Clock Tower in 500 AD. The Wandering Sea and Atlas stuck to the old ways of the Age of Gods, but the three groups still remained together as the Mage's Association.<br>  The Magi of the Wandering Sea sought to isolate themselves from the reach of both Gods and mankind. Thus their entire island vanished from the universe, drifting away in space and time. No one can observe or interact with it except via the Five Gates at its entrance.<br>  As of the formation of the Clock Tower, they ceased communication with the Association.<br>  The Wandering Sea manifests once a year in each era, but it is merely a shadow of what the "Wandering Sea that once was". The true nature of the Wandering Sea, or the&nbsp;"True Wandering Sea" refers to what lies behind the Five Gates at the Wandering Sea's   entrance.<br><br>  Having opposed the modernization of Magecraft along with Atlas in 20 AD, their primary rule is the rejection of the modern advancement of Magecraft, only recognizing that of the Age of Gods. but there are no restrictions on what they can actually use, such as Western Magecraft or <a data-href="Philosophy Magecraft" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/philosophy-magecraft.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Philosophy Magecraft</a>. Atlas-style Alchemy is probably the only thing they don't do. It is said that the focus of their research is human bodily modification, but other details are unknown.<br>  Most individuals within the Wandering Sea seem to possess the same power to "crush and scatter countless&nbsp;Lords".<br><br>Recruitment into the Wandering Sea is rare, those recruited from even the prestigious Clock Tower Magi able to be counted on a single hand. While qualifying to arrive upon the island for its once per year opening is difficult, the actual means of qualification is to simply be present at the location of one of the Five Gates when they are open.<br><br>  Info known by higher positions or specific fields in The Mage's Association.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-wandering-sea.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Wandering Sea.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:15:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250212212454.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250212212454.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The World of Type Moon]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Nasuverse is equivalent to our own, the main difference is that magic is real and that a lot of people are doing their best to keep it a secret from the common man, for<br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Mystery" data-href="Mystery" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/mystery.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">good reason</a>.<br>
There are some differences between the different worlds in the Nasuverse for example the Tsukihime world is different than the Fate one bc there was a BIG split in the timeline caused by a single mf (kinda), that has some impacts on Alaya.<br>
The will of humanity is stronger in the Fate world than the one in Tsukihime that is what mainly causes the differences such as servants existing in Fate but not Tsukihime. Tho that's not really necessarily important rn. All you need to know is that the world of the campaign is set in a middle ground between the two (heh just like strange fake fr fr).<br>One very important thing about the lore document is that I'll be adding some highlights for each paragraph (or the whole section) to indicate what your characters might know and what they won't, this is the main reason Im actually making this other than like summarizing shit.<br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.<br>
  Info known by higher positions or specific fields in The Mage's Association.<br>
  Info known by people of the church.<br>
  Info known by Specific divisions of the church of the Church.<br>
  Nobody knows this.<br>Table of Contents<br>
<br><a data-href="The planes of Existence" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-planes-of-existence.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The planes of Existence</a>
<br><a data-href="Mystery" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/mystery.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Mystery</a>
<br><a data-href="Gaia" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/gaia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Gaia</a>
<br><a data-href="Alaya" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/alaya.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Alaya</a>
<br><a data-href="The Counter Force" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-counter-force.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Counter Force</a>
<br><a data-href="Magecraft" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/magecraft.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magecraft</a>
<br><a data-href="Psychics" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/psychics.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Psychics</a>
<br><a data-href="The Magi" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-magi.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Magi</a>
<br><a data-href="The Mage's Association" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-mage's-association.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Mage's Association</a>
<br><a data-href="The Church" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-church.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Church</a>
<br><a data-href="Other Factions" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/other-factions.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Other Factions</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dead Apostles" data-href="Dead Apostles" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/dead-apostles.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dead Apostles (Vampires)</a>
<br><a data-href="The Holy Grail War" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-holy-grail-war.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Holy Grail War</a>
<br><a data-href="Pf2e to Type Moon Conversion" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/pf2e-to-type-moon-conversion.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Pf2e to Type Moon Conversion</a>
<br><a data-href="Current Events" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/current-events.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Current Events</a>
<br>A small number of things may have been changed to simplify or due to reasons.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/the-world-of-type-moon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The World of Type Moon.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 19:54:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[True Ancestors]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>  Unique existences even among the vampires, the True Ancestors are classified as Elementals, said to be the original bloodsucking species independently created by the Planet as its sense of touch.<br>    Elemental royalty, they are born as vampiric creatures, however, unlike the Dead Apostles and other blood-sucking species, the root of their bloodlust is psychological rather than physical, since their body does not have any need blood. <br>    All True Ancestors possess power beyond human comprehension from the moment they are born. There are few who can match them in terms of strength, speed and endurance. They are a completely different species from the originally human Dead Apostles, sunlight does not faze them — they are beings infinitely close to a perfect&nbsp;immortality.<br>    Very few Conceptual Weapons can harm them. All vampires can ignore damage from most sources as their body will revert to the pre-damaged state rapidly, a Conceptual Weapon such as the Black Keys used by members of the Holy Church nullifies this ability. At night they are almost invulnerable, and their power is at its peak during the full Moon. And unlike Dead apostles as they are still living creatures they can procreate.<br>    The True Ancestors can use&nbsp;Marble Phantasm, an ability similar to Reality Marbles but not the same, it can literally change reality to create any naturally occurring effect.<br>    The True Ancestors receives backup from the planet as part of the Counter Force.  As they receive backup from the planet, it can be said that the limits of their actions are the limits of nature itself. If the planet is thought of as a single organism they are like its white blood cells, regarding the humans who consume nature as an element that must be exterminated.<br><br>    Brunestud of the Crimson Moon offered a pact to the planet: in exchange of being allowed to live on Earth, Crimson Moon would allow the creation of a self-defense mechanism for the planet based on him. From this pact between <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Gaia" data-href="Gaia" href="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/gaia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Ultimate One</a> of the Moon and the will of the Earth the True Ancestors were born as a Counter Force, created for the purpose of returning the planet to its original state, before the corruption caused by humans.<br><br>   In 300 AD, he was fucking Soloed by Kischur THE GOAT Zelretch Schweinorg wielding the Second Magic. He tried to pull the Moon to collide with Earth but it was pushed back by Zelretch's Magic, so it was unable to affect the planet. With all of his power, Brunestud did not foresee being defeated by a human, but lost to Zelretch due to being too late in understanding the power of Magic, "a rule outside of the rules."<br><br>True Ancestors are fundamentally copies of the Crimson Moon with minds and bodies modeled after humans, the latter done so under the principle that it would be best for them to resemble those who they are supposed to rule over. Because Crimson Moon was their basis, the True Ancestors have inherited a terrible flaw from the original:&nbsp;Vampiric Impulses, the desire to suck Human Blood.<br>A purely psychological impulse that pushes them to suck the blood of others, because there is no physical reason behind those impulses there is no definite cure for them. Thus, the True Ancestors need to sleep through their childhood until they are mature enough to have self-control. The True Ancestors must use their own powers to keep the vampiric impulses in check. That is why they never fight at 100% as most of their powers is already being used to restrain themselves.<br>
However, because there is no end to the vampiric impulses, they do not disappear and instead accumulate with time. Eventually, those impulses will become too powerful to be restrained and threaten to take over. When they reach their limit, the True Ancestors choose eternal sleep for themselves.<br>But for those who have succumbed to their urges and drank human blood, they lose their ability to restrain themselves and lose their sanity, they are dubbed Demon Lords which is and are killed by their own kind.<br>
It is believed that there are no True ancestors that have sucked blood and stayed the same mentally.<br><br>As Demon Lords no longer needed to suppress their thirst, they could employ their powers to their full extent and therefore vastly overwhelm their still restrained kin. It was with the purpose of their elimination that the True Ancestors caused the birth of Arcueid Brunestud.<br>
she was raised as killing machine that slumbers until one of a Demon Lord appears, in or order to dispatch them as swiftly as possible.<br>
Although she is regarded as The princess of Vampires by her kind, she is more despised and feared than anything, they truly only see her as a Missile they can use to exterminate their fallen brethren.<br><br><br>  Anyone who studied magecraft knows this, whether from the Mage's Association, the church, or a standalone guy.<br>
  Info known by higher positions or specific fields in The Mage's Association.<br>
  Info known by Specific divisions of the church of the Church.]]></description><link>https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/true-ancestors.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">True Ancestors.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[MD]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 18:08:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250214165852.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mdthesimp.github.io/Fate-Campaign-Lore/images/pasted-image-20250214165852.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>